<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Information Book</string>
    <string name="united_kingdom">
        <b>Capital</b>\t\t\t\t\t\t: London \n
        <b>Largest City</b>\t\t\t\: London \n
        <b>National Language</b>\t: English \n
        <b>Total Area</b>\t\t\t\t\: 242,495 km2 \n
        <b>Currency</b>\t\t\t\t\t\: GBP \n\n

        \t\t The United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland, simply known as the United Kingdom (UK) or Britain, is a country in Northwestern Europe, off the north-western coast of the continental mainland. It comprises England, Scotland, Wales, and Northern Ireland. It includes the island of Great Britain, the north-eastern part of the island of Ireland, and most of the smaller islands within the British Isles. Northern Ireland shares a land border with the Republic of Ireland; otherwise, the United Kingdom is surrounded by the Atlantic Ocean, the North Sea, the English Channel, the Celtic Sea and the Irish Sea. The total area of the United Kingdom is 242,495 square kilometres (93,628 sq mi), with an estimated 2023 population of over 68 million people.

\n\n\t\t The United Kingdom has evolved from a series of annexations, unions and separations of constituent countries over several hundred years. The Treaty of Union between the Kingdom of England (which also included Wales) and the Kingdom of Scotland in 1707 resulted in their unification to become the Kingdom of Great Britain. Its union in 1801 with the Kingdom of Ireland created the United Kingdom of Great Britain and Ireland. Most of Ireland seceded from the UK in 1922, leaving the present United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland, which formally adopted its name in 1927. The nearby Isle of Man, Guernsey and Jersey are not part of the UK, being Crown Dependencies, but the British government is responsible for their defence and international representation. The British Overseas Territories are fourteen territories with a constitutional and historical link with the United Kingdom. The UK became the world\'s first industrialised country and was the foremost power during the 19th and early 20th centuries, a period of unchallenged global hegemony known as "Pax Britannica".[22][23] The British Empire which, at its height in the 1920s, encompassed almost a quarter of the world\'s landmass and population, and was the largest empire in history was a part of the core Anglophonic world, British influence can be observed in the language, culture, legal and political systems of many of its former colonies.

\n\n\t\t The United Kingdom is a constitutional monarchy and parliamentary democracy. Its capital and largest city is London (also the capital of England), a megacity which serves as one of the world\'s two main financial centres. Edinburgh, Cardiff, and Belfast are the national capitals of Scotland, Wales, and Northern Ireland respectively. Other major cities include Birmingham, Manchester, Leeds, Glasgow, Sheffield, and Liverpool. The UK consists of three distinct legal jurisdictions: England and Wales, Scotland, and Northern Ireland. This is due to these areas retaining their existing legal systems even after joining the UK.[27] Since 1998, Scotland, Wales, and Northern Ireland also have their own devolved governments and legislatures, each with varying powers.

\n\n\t\t The UK is one of the world\s great powers, exerting significant political power and influence globally. In particular, economic, military, scientific and cultural power. It has the world\'s sixth-largest economy by nominal gross domestic product (GDP), and the tenth-largest by purchasing power parity (PPP). The UK ranks highly for international measures of quality of life, economic freedom, innovation, healthcare and education. However, the UK has among the highest levels of income inequality in Europe and the OECD, and is one of the most regionally unequal high-income countries in the world. It is a recognised nuclear-weapon state and is the foremost military power in Europe. The UK has been a permanent member of the UN Security Council since its first session in 1946. It is a member of the Commonwealth of Nations, the Council of Europe, the G7, the OECD, NATO, the Five Eyes, and AUKUS. It was a member of the EU until its withdrawal in 2020.
    </string>

    <string name="india">
    <b>Capital</b>\t\t\t\t\t\t: New Delhi \n
    <b>Largest City</b>\t\t\t\: Mumbai \n
    <b>National Language</b>\t: Hindi \n
    <b>Total Area</b>\t\t\t\t\: 3,287,263 km2 \n
    <b>Currency</b>\t\t\t\t\t\: INR \n\n

     \t\t India, officially the Republic of India (ISO: Bhārat Gaṇarājya), is a country in South Asia. It is the seventh-largest country by area; the most populous country and the world\'s most populous democracy. Bounded by the Indian Ocean on the south, the Arabian Sea on the southwest, and the Bay of Bengal on the southeast, it shares land borders with Pakistan to the west; China, Nepal, and Bhutan to the north; and Bangladesh and Myanmar to the east. In the Indian Ocean, India is in the vicinity of Sri Lanka and the Maldives; its Andaman and Nicobar Islands share a maritime border with Thailand, Myanmar, and Indonesia.

\n\n\t\t Modern humans arrived on the Indian subcontinent from Africa no later than 55,000 years ago.Their long occupation, initially in varying forms of isolation as hunter-gatherers, has made the region highly diverse, second only to Africa in human genetic diversity. Settled life emerged on the subcontinent in the western margins of the Indus river basin 9,000 years ago, evolving gradually into the Indus Valley Civilisation of the third millennium BCE. By 1200 BCE, an archaic form of Sanskrit, an Indo-European language, had diffused into India from the northwest. Its evidence today is found in the hymns of the Rigveda. Preserved by an oral tradition that was resolutely vigilant, the Rigveda records the dawning of Hinduism in India.[38] The Dravidian languages of India were supplanted in the northern and western regions. By 400 BCE, stratification and exclusion by caste had emerged within Hinduism, and Buddhism and Jainism had arisen, proclaiming social orders unlinked to heredity. Early political consolidations gave rise to the loose-knit Maurya and Gupta Empires based in the Ganges Basin. Their collective era was suffused with wide-ranging creativity, but also marked by the declining status of women, and the incorporation of untouchability into an organised system of belief. In South India, the Middle kingdoms exported Dravidian-languages scripts and religious cultures to the kingdoms of Southeast Asia.

\n\n\t\t In the early medieval era, Christianity, Islam, Judaism, and Zoroastrianism became established on India\'s southern and western coasts. Muslim armies from Central Asia intermittently overran India\'s northern plains, eventually founding the Delhi Sultanate, and drawing northern India into the cosmopolitan networks of medieval Islam. In the 15th century, the Vijayanagara Empire created a long-lasting composite Hindu culture in south India. In the Punjab, Sikhism emerged, rejecting institutionalised religion. The Mughal Empire, in 1526, ushered in two centuries of relative peace, leaving a legacy of luminous architecture. Gradually expanding rule of the British East India Company followed, turning India into a colonial economy, but also consolidating its sovereignty. British Crown rule began in 1858. The rights promised to Indians were granted slowly, but technological changes were introduced, and modern ideas of education and the public life took root. A pioneering and influential nationalist movement emerged, which was noted for nonviolent resistance and became the major factor in ending British rule. In 1947 the British Indian Empire was partitioned into two independent dominions, a Hindu-majority Dominion of India and a Muslim-majority Dominion of Pakistan, amid large-scale loss of life and an unprecedented migration.

\n\n\t\t India has been a federal republic since 1950, governed through a democratic parliamentary system. It is a pluralistic, multilingual and multi-ethnic society. India\'s population grew from 361 million in 1951 to almost 1.4 billion in 2022. During the same time, its nominal per capita income increased from US$64 annually to US$1,498, and its literacy rate from 16.6% to 74%. From being a comparatively destitute country in 1951,[66] India has become a fast-growing major economy and a hub for information technology services, with an expanding middle class. It has a space programme which includes several planned or completed extraterrestrial missions. Indian movies, music, and spiritual teachings play an increasing role in global culture.[68] India has substantially reduced its rate of poverty, though at the cost of increasing economic inequality. India is a nuclear-weapon state, which ranks high in military expenditure. It has disputes over Kashmir with its neighbours, Pakistan and China, unresolved since the mid-20th century.Among the socio-economic challenges India faces are gender inequality, child malnutrition, and rising levels of air pollution. India\'s land is megadiverse, with four biodiversity hotspots. Its forest cover comprises 21.7% of its area. India\'s wildlife, which has traditionally been viewed with tolerance in India\'s culture, is supported among these forests, and elsewhere, in protected habitats.


    </string>

    <string name="taj_mahal">
    \t\t The Taj Mahal (\'Crown of the Palace\') is an ivory-white marble mausoleum on the right bank of the river Yamuna in Agra, Uttar Pradesh, India. It was commissioned in 1631 by the fifth Mughal emperor, Shah Jahan  to house the tomb of his favourite wife, Mumtaz Mahal; it also houses the tomb of Shah Jahan himself. The tomb is the centrepiece of a 17-hectare  complex, which includes a mosque and a guest house, and is set in formal gardens bounded on three sides by a crenellated wall.

\n\n\t\t Construction of the mausoleum was essentially completed in 1643, but work continued on other phases of the project for another 10 years. The Taj Mahal complex is believed to have been completed in its entirety in 1653 at a cost estimated at the time to be around ₹32 million, which in 2023 would be approximately ₹35 billion. The construction project employed some 20,000 artisans under the guidance of a board of architects led by Ustad Ahmad Lahori, the emperor\'s court architect. Various types of symbolism have been employed in the Taj to reflect natural beauty and divinity.

\n\n\t\t The Taj Mahal was designated as a UNESCO World Heritage Site in 1983 for being "the jewel of Muslim art in India and one of the universally admired masterpieces of the world\'s heritage". It is regarded by many as the best example of Mughal architecture and a symbol of India\'s rich history. The Taj Mahal attracts more than 6 million visitors a year, and in 2007 it was declared a winner of the New 7 Wonders of the World (2000–2007) initiative.
    </string>
</resources>